# Jeremiah Snow

**■** jlsnow301@pm.me | **□** 206-375-0003 | **♀** Seattle, WA | **९** https://jlsnow301.github.io

### Skills

**Programming Languages** 

JavaScript, TypeScript, Rust, Python, Go, HTML, CSS

Frameworks Services React, NextJS, Astro, NodeJS, Deno AWS, GCP, Azure, Git, Supabase

Data Postgres, MySQL, PlanetScale, Prisma, Drizzle

## Projects \_\_\_\_\_

Meal Swap

TypeScript, React Native, Supabase

MOBILE APPLICATION DEVELOPED IN REACT NATIVE - EXPO. LEAD DEVELOPER. CURRENTLY UNDER NDA DURING DEVELOPMENT.

Private

Datagrid TypeScript, React Table, Zod, MUI

A USER-FRIENDLY REACT COMPONENT BUILT WITH TYPESCRIPT. INTEGRATED POWERFUL LIBRARIES TO SEAMLESSLY GENERATE DATA GRIDS WITH AUTOMATICALLY GENERATED TYPE-SAFE FORMS, PROVIDING DEVELOPERS WITH A STREAMLINED EXPERIENCE.

github.com/jlsnow301/datagrid

Ambient Noise JavaScript, React Native

Developed a React Native prototype app for Zillow, enabling prospective homeowners to record and listen to audio tours. Implemented advanced features to gauge road noise and other environmental factors, providing users with additional dimensions of data to enhance their purchasing experience.

github.com/jlsnow301/ambient-noise

## Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

Pareto Cyber Remote

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

06/2022 - 08/2023

- React 18, Go backend, Postgres DB and AWS.
- Made significant upgrades to the front end architecture which lead to an improved UI, a 36-point increase in Lighthouse scores, and build time reduction of 97%.
- · Worked across all layers of development, including API creation, database management, and product demonstration.
- · Successfully converted codebase to TypeScript, improving overall code quality and maintainability.

TG Station Remote

MAINTAINER - UI

03/2019 - Present

- Tech stack of TypeScript React and a C-like language with OOP principles (Byond).
- Performed thorough code reviews in an open-source GitHub repository which average 120 new pull requests per week from 1,197 contributors, ensuring code quality and adherence to best practices.
- Collaborated closely with industry professionals to design and create visually appealing user experiences, enhancing the overall usability and aesthetics of the application.
- Revamped and upgraded key user-facing dialogs with secure and feature-rich alternatives, resulting in a significant enhancement of the user experience and ensuring robust data security for TG Station's platform.

### **Education**

North Seattle College Seattle, WA

BAS IN APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT GPA: 3.4

01/2019 - 06/2021

• Developed a strong foundation in computer science through hands-on projects spanning various disciplines, including: Web & mobile development, data structures & algorithms, data science, and cloud services.

Belmont College

Saint Clairsville, OH

01/2016 - 06/2018

AAS IN COMPUTER NETWORKING GPA: 3.7

• Completed an accelerated computer networking course with a focus on CISCO technologies, gaining a strong foundation in UNIX, networking principles, and computer hardware.